<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hipaa_full_text">Digital HIPAA Authorization for Disclosure of Personal Health Information (PHI)\n\nBy checking the box and electronically signing below, I provide my express written authorization for COPD FUEL (\"Company\") to use and disclose my Personal Health Information (PHI) as described in this Authorization.\n\n1. Persons Authorized to Receive Information\nI authorize COPD FUEL to disclose my PHI to the individual(s) I designate, which may include:\n- My physician or other health care provider\n- A family member or relative\n- A caregiver or other person I choose\nI may identify specific individuals within the app or through a separate written designation.\n\n2. Information Authorized for Disclosure\nI authorize COPD FUEL to disclose the following categories of my PHI, including related records, data, communications, or documentation (check all that apply):\n- Diagnoses, medical conditions, and symptom tracking data\n- Medication and prescription records\n- Laboratory, diagnostic, and test results\n- Clinical notes, treatment plans, and care coordination documentation\n- Diet, nutrition plans, dietary logs, and recommendations\n- Medical equipment usage data (oxygen therapy, inhalers, respiratory devices, etc.)\n\n3. Purpose of Disclosure\nThis Authorization permits COPD FUEL to disclose my PHI for care coordination, communication with individuals I designate, and any other purpose I specify within the app or in writing.\n\n4. Individual Rights and Acknowledgments\nI understand that:\n- This Authorization is voluntary. I am not required to sign it.\n- I may refuse to sign this Authorization.\n- I may revoke this Authorization at any time through the COPD FUEL platform or by emailing ingeniousmedsolutions6@gmail.com. Revocation will not apply to uses or disclosures made before the effective date of revocation.\n- COPD FUEL may rely on this Authorization until a valid revocation is received.\n- Once my PHI is disclosed to the person(s) I designate, it may no longer be protected under the HIPAA Privacy Rule and may be subject to redisclosure.\n- I have the right to receive a copy of this signed Authorization in electronic form.\n\n5. Expiration\nThis Authorization remains valid for as long as my COPD FUEL account is active, unless I revoke it earlier. It will terminate upon my written revocation or upon closure or deactivation of my account.\n\n6. Account Security\nI am responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of my account credentials. COPD FUEL will not be liable for unauthorized access resulting from my sharing or failing to safeguard my login credentials.\n\n7. Electronic Consent\nBy checking the box and electronically signing, I confirm that I have read and understand this Authorization, I agree to the disclosure of my PHI as described above, and I understand my rights as outlined herein.</string>
</resources>
